The mustache rides. Again.
Super Troopers 2 is a comedy, crime, mystery film directed by Jay Chandrasekhar.
When an international border dispute arises between the U.S.
and Canada, the Super Troopers- Mac, Thorny, Foster, Rabbit and Farva, are called
in to set up a new Highway Patrol station in the disputed area.
Arcot 'Thorny' Ramathorn, played by Jay Chandrasekhar.
Rodney 'Rod' Farva, played by Kevin Heffernan.
MacIntyre 'Mac' Womack, played by Steve Lemme.
Robbie 'Rabbit' Roto, played by Erik Stolhanske.
Carl Foster, played by Paul Soter.
Genevieve Aubois/Andrea Spooner, played by Emmanuelle Chriqui.
Super Troopers 2 is a 2018 American comedy film directed by Jay Chandrasekhar.
A sequel to the 2001 film Super Troopers, the film was written by and stars the Broken Lizard comedy team,
made up of Chandrasekhar, Kevin Heffernan, Steve Lemme, Paul Soter and Erik Stolhanske.
The plot follows the Super Troopers being called upon to set up a new Highway Patrol station
when an international border dispute arises between the United States and Canada.
The film had a troubled development period as studios were skeptical that a sequel,
produced over a decade after the original, would find an audience.
After a successful crowdfunding campaign produced $2 million in seed money in 24 hours (and $4.7 million overall), the
film was greenlit, and principal photography began in the Central Massachusetts area on October 23, 2015.
The film was released in the United States on April
20, 2018, by Fox Searchlight Pictures.
The film explores themes of police, cop, sequel,
aftercreditsstinger, duringcreditsstinger.
The tone is lighthearted and mind_bending.